

CONTACT

+33 (0)6 23 16 19 06



audreyboucher95@gmail.com



Nantes, France

SKILLS

- HTML / CSS / JS
- ReactJS / VueJS / Redux
- Typescript
- Unit/e2e tests & Cypress
- UI/UX design
- Autonomy & adaptability
- Attentiveness & patience
- Empathy & communication

LANGUAGES

- French (Native)
- English (Fluent)

HOBBIES

- Sports: triathlon, yoga
- Japanese animation
- Plant-based and creative cooking

AUDREY BOUCHER

REACT FRONT-END DEVELOPER



PROFILE

I'm a JavaScript warrior with a solid experience in frontend development (particularly ReactJS) and a strong UX/UI foundation. My love for challenges and eagerness to learn work wonders for me to translate mockups and ideas into proper functional features.



WORK EXPERIENCE

React front-end developer

2021 - 2023

AB Tasty, Paris & Nantes

- Creation of customer interface's modules
- Conducting intra and inter-team code reviews
- Bug fixes
- Unit & e2e testing
- Teamwork using the agile method precepts

Technical support engineer (Customer support)

2017 - 2021

AB Tasty, Paris & Madrid

- Customer service
- Popularization of technical terms
- Estimation of the feasibility/duration of a task based on provided specifications
- · Technical training of customer advisor teams
- Creation of a command line to save time on team's repetitive

Front-end developer

2013 - 2015

Le Parisien, Saint-Ouen

- Creation of emailing templates
- Development of event-related UI & features
- Migration from Symfony2 to Symfony3



EDUCATION

Design and development of IT solutions

2015 - 2017

42 school | Paris, France

Bachelor Multimedia Project Manager

2012 - 2015

IESA Multimédia | Paris, France